That's
那是
Little bit
一点
I'm using because I am not
我正在使用，因为我不在
Probably my favourite
可能是我的最爱
Slightly
For the heart
为了心脏
Put butter on both sides of butter
在黄油的两面都放黄油
You put it on the bread
你把它放在面包上
This is going to be really gross
这真的很毛
Play Jesus
扮演耶稣
Individually
个别地
News
新闻
It'll be great
会很棒
You can have some
你可以吃一些
That is 6 and 6 slices of cheese
那是6片和6片奶酪
Go on
继续
And it's summer again
又是夏天
Turn up to
转到
As hi is it
嗨，是
Ok something is definitely burning now
好吧，现在肯定有东西在燃烧
The more flipping you do the better because it is
翻转得越多越好，因为
It's a bit crispy brie
有点脆
I think it's ok
我觉得还可以
I personally like my
我个人喜欢我的
I did not cook this evening we are all you see are you still see slices that's the incorrect way to do it
今晚我没煮，我们只见你了吗，你仍然看到切成薄片的方法是不正确的。
I'm going to
我要去
Underneath
Does this is what's going to save you from burning
这是什么可以让您免于燃烧吗
Do you want to butter both sides
你想在两面都涂黄油吗
There's no point in trying to make a grilled cheese without
没有烧烤就没有意义
So we have a variety of
所以我们有各种各样的
Archies
Monster
怪物
The butter in the pan I have to be careful cuz you better can burn
锅里的黄油我要小心一点，因为你最好能燃烧
The other side
另一边
Too much
太多了
Siri
Sunny House
阳光屋
Very good
很好
The big question is the UK
最大的问题是英国
I like the cut
我喜欢剪
On the diagonal
在对角线上
I'm a stranger
我是一个陌生人
Just logo butter
只是徽标黄油
On the pan
在锅上
Is it raining at night
晚上下雨吗
Smokey rideaway
烟熏之旅
I think is the key for the really classicroses
我认为这是真正经典玫瑰的关键
Is that butter has
那黄油有吗
Ingredients that are not just your fat
不仅仅是脂肪的成分
In the pan
在锅里
Put the mixture experiment
进行混合实验
I'm going to go with a slice of Cheddar
我要去切达干酪
And also
并且
Because it's really really good soft melting cheese
因为它真的是非常好的软融化奶酪
Let it go
放手吧
To keep an eye on the butter what were looking for is no smoke I'm looking for the foaming and listening for the
为了留心黄油，我所寻找的是无烟，我正在寻找泡沫，并聆听
I'm just doing a bit of a shake to make sure that nothing stuck to the pan
我只是在摇一摇，以确保没有东西粘在锅上
So what we gonna do is go ahead
所以我们要做的是继续前进
This
这个
Remind me to melt before the bread buns
提醒我在面包之前融化
We are ready to go
我们准备出发了
Can we have it that's are you saying she's in there
我们能得到那是你在说她在那里吗
Play some LT with Cheddar and monster in there too
也可以在切达和怪物那里玩一些LT